the fundamentals good to have you on
board uh sorab and entire banking space
because it's not just uh you know the
front large cap
Banks I mean look I think the the best
way to think one day the business cycle
will weaken and if you don't have the
strongest players then you could
potentially get beaten up in the
downturn of the business cycle so so
we've historically gone for for the
strongest banks at nbfcs the Bajaj
finances and Chola mums on the nbfc side
HDFC Bank kotak bank axis Bank have
historically been have been a big place
over the last couple of months for the
first time in Marcel's history we built
a a meaningful position in ic bank will
carry on building that home first and we
have mass financials as well and and
he's right ahead of them that's an
interesting one you know sort of Since
since you mentioned home first I want to
like dig a little deeper into that why
holders big fans of what Mr J has done
there buil a buil up on distribution and
whil East Zone and North uh a lot of
money on that and we have to thank Mr
Jun Wala for building bril will give
them some competition but it's still a
category large enough for for you know
two credible players laala and Boro and
do justice to the quality of the product
that's literally put on the
table and uh s know going through the
recent additions and exits besides what
I see is that you've added iic Lombard
General a home first Finance we've
talked about over the last six months as
Mr Panda has come in as a regulator and
I think there's a lot of stuff happening
Ina which is very very encouraging for
high quality multi-line insurers like I
kudos to the regulator for coming and
positively shaking things up in the
insurance sector in Abo's case uh
there's a couple of things which which
sort of worried us over the last year or
so uh the first is rapid erosion in in
abt's market share and therefore in its
cash flows and profitability and it was
woring to see how quickly the duper
Stone are changes in the boardroom I
think in the last five role um and that
sort of boardroom churn is always a
little concerning you've been fairly um
uh you know you've continued to talk
about suprit as well as Aisha Motors um
what's the Outlook into that you know
some of the other large caps say you
know why not the likes of emm or a
maruti that are looking at an ev4 like a
Tata Motors portfolios now on auto
ancillaries right as I think you're
alluding to the auto recovery seems
seems to be on its way I'm not sure the
auto are roaring quite yet but at least
the last four five dryan team uh
consistent roc's north of 20% Which is
and a world leading position now in in
cables in cables going into our Su
position in our Rising Giants portfolio
and in our midcap portfolio that's a
significant play and our hope is that as
the oem's AA motor longstanding holding
in some of our portfolios I think not
the best the only credible player in the
Premier end of the of the of the
motorbike market and why not Eminem why
not maruti Suzuki U we've sort of
struggled to understand their pricing
power right unless you can charge
premium prices unless you can charge
premium prices uh you you're not going
to make uh 30 40% and you want to
consistently have upgrade Cycles which
are world class oems who actually
command premium pricing which becomes um
S I want to talk about Titan and I want
to understand whether you've turned
formula right uh every stock has a
position size that it merits has made in
the last decade or so so Titan has a
very large weight in our portfolio uh it
had a tremendous rally and and that
rally pulled pushed the portfolio weight
above where it should be and therefore
we rebalanced it down uh there is no
dimin in our conviction on title remains
a very large holding and hopefully it'll
make money on what we thought it
merited you know um just starting to
take to some of them for example Samir
hel these companies carefully to see
whether they can follow through on the
commitment because it's one thing and
I'm hoping uh praying uh indeed that we
see uh the world and in the stock price
sense of the
world little champs I'm wondering who's
behind these creative names right okay
now I think the the the investment
committee gets together and and decides
um you know what is the theme that we
want to convey because you know people
like you you guys are busy people and if
we want to it's easy for us to con
convey the essence of the product in two
words rather than is the best small Cap
Fund in the country so try to come up
with the name which conveys the essence
goog I was throwing it you anyway s good
to have okay let's just revisit where
the market has settled in at it seemed
like it's uh